New York Review of Books Records
New York Review of Books Records
- Manuscripts
  - Miscellaneous letters, unassignable or unused
    - James Scully to the Editors, typescript, reproduction, revised (Box 35)
    - Harvey Schapiro to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Geoffrey Barraclough replies (Box 35)
    - David E. Sopher to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Owen Thomas to the Editors (Box 35)
    - James Toledano to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Alan Trachteberg to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Parker Tyler to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Marius Bewley replies to Veysey (Box 35)
    - John C. Weston to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Marshall Windmiller to the Editors, typescript reproduction (Box 35)
    - Karen Wittgenstein to the Editors (Box 35)
    - Wayne D. Wolchek (Box 35)
  - Miscellaneous poems, unassignable or unused
    - Neal Ascherson, no title (Box 35)
    - Kenneth Burk, "Statements of Attitude," "Major Lobotomy", galley (Box 35)
    - Richard Eberhart, "The Killer: On the Assassination of President Kennedy" (Box 35)
    - Frederick Seidel, "My Friend Anne Hutchinson", typescript copy revised (Box 35)
    - Richard Wilbur, "The Lilacs" (Box 35)
  - Unidentifiable fragments
    - Review of book on Apollinaire (?) (Box 35)
    - Review of book on Middle East, typescript reproduction galley inserts (Box 35)
    - Review of book on English Parliament (Box 35)
    - Review of unknown book (Box 35)
    - Fragment from April 16, 1964 folder (?) (Box 35)
- Miscellany
  - Ayer, A.J., untitled book, 1965 (?); galley page proofs, with marginal comments by Anthony Quine, printed material annotated (Box 35)
  - Thomson, Virgil (?), Memoirs (?), chapters 3-13, typescript copy revised; 3 folders (Box 35)
  - Index
    - Vol. I and Vol. II, 1965; published material, typescript copy revised (Box 35)
    - Vol. I - Vol. XI, 1969; published material (Box 35)
    - Vol. XII - Vol. XV, 1969; 1970; published material (Box 35)